The biggest
poison in
us is
regret. I
think there
are a
lot of
people that
have dreams
and aspirations
of things
that they
always wanted
to do,
but it
wasn't the
right time
or they
didn't have
enough money
or they
didn't have
enough experience.
It's never
the right
time. You're
never going
to have
the right
experience. And
all of
a sudden
you wake
up and
you're And
you're like,
God, I
wish I
could have
done it.
It's what
you don't
do that
screws with
you later
on. I
get one
shot at
this life.
This is
it. And
I don't
want to
go through
life being
the version
of me.
I don't
want to
look back
and be
like and
be like,
I didn't
do that.
There's so
much I
want to
do and
I love
life so
much, I
don't want
to miss
it.